<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-06-05T10:20:42+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Offer</title><subtitle>Offers, Deals, Promo codes, Freebies. 
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Get Rs 30 Free Paytm Cash on Purchase of every 1Kg Tide Detergent Pack</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/06/05/Get-Rs-30-Free-Paytm-Cash-on-Purchase-of-every-1Kg-Tide-Detergent-Pack.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Get Rs 30 Free Paytm Cash on Purchase of every 1Kg Tide Detergent Pack" /><published>2017-06-05T10:15:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-06-05T10:15:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/06/05/Get-Rs-30-Free-Paytm-Cash-on-Purchase-of-every-1Kg-Tide-Detergent-Pack</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/06/05/Get-Rs-30-Free-Paytm-Cash-on-Purchase-of-every-1Kg-Tide-Detergent-Pack.html">&lt;h4&gt;How to Get Rs 30 Free Paytm Cash from Tide Plus Pack&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) First of all, Visit on your Nearest General Store which has new packs of Tide Plus 1Kg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Buy a Tide Plus Pack of 1Kg (Make sure Paytm Tide offer is mentioned on it (See screenshot below).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s30.postimg.org/fwy1gx6e9/IMG_20170507_185300-450x242.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;tide&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Buy Tide Plus and Open the Pack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Look for a Promocode inside the Pack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Now &lt;a href=&quot;https://paytm.com/TidePlus&quot;&gt;Visit Paytm Website Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Enter your Promo code (which you got from Tide Plus Pack).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Login/Sign up on Paytm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) That’s it, Rs 30 will be credited to your Paytm wallet Instantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) Now You can use it for Mobile Recharge or Bill Payments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Terms &amp;amp; Conditions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) This Offer is being conducted by Procter &amp;amp; Gamble Home Products Private Limited (herein after referred to as ‘P&amp;amp;G’) in association with One97 Communications Ltd. (‘One97’ or Paytm’, collectively referred to as ‘the Organizer’) on One97’s platform, namely www.Paytm.com (‘website’).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) This Offer is valid in India from 1st May 2017 to 31st August 2017 for 1 KG Pack pack and 1st June 2017 to 30th September 2017 for 500 gm pack (‘Offer Period’) on purchase of Tide Plus Packs referred to as “Products” and on limited stocks only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) User would not be able to avail the offer after that, even if the product is available and within the product shelf life as mentioned on the individual packet itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) The promo code cannot be redeemed after the expiry of the Offer Period and you agree to waive off right of redemption on the date of expiry of the Offer Period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) The Offer is valid for the citizens of India (except the employees and family members of P&amp;amp;G and the organizer, their associate companies, their joint venture partners, its co-packers, their distributors, their agents, their advertising and promotional agencies and their auditors.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) To avail benefits of the offer, a Customer needs to buy a pack of Tide Plus. The offer is available on the 500 gm and 1 Kg pack of Tide Plus only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) After purchasing the Products, the Customer will get a unique promo code (“Code”) on the inner surface of the product packet. After getting this promo Code, the participant can participate in the Offer and avail Paytm Cash. Paytm cash is the term used to define Paytm cash that the Customer gets when he/she applies the promo code on Paytm website/app. The cash earned this way will be ‘credited’ in the Paytm wallet and can be redeemed against any purchases from the vendors accepting paytm cash or the same can be redeemed on the paytm website/app. No cash would be given in lieu of Paytm cash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) On successful application of the promo code Rs 15 for 500 gm and Rs 30 for 1 Kg would be added to user’s Paytm wallet within 24 hours. Although, neither P&amp;amp;G nor the Organiser will be liable for any delay in actual redemption, under this Offer, reflecting in the customers’ account due to any unforeseen circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) It is the sole responsibility of the Organiser to deliver the added money to the Customer’s Paytm wallet. Due to any reason if the Customer is not able to add money, he/she has to approach the Paytm customer care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10) All customer related queries for this Offer can be addressed to care@paytm.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;11) Each promo code can be used once.
One user/mobile No. can avail this offer only once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12) In case of any conflict between terms and conditions/ instructions printed on the pack/mobile message/ insert/ voucher and the website, terms and conditions printed on website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">How to Get Rs 30 Free Paytm Cash from Tide Plus Pack</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">FreeCharge – Get Rs 25 Cashback on Rs 25 Mobile Recharge (account Specific)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/freecharge/2017/06/05/FreeCharge-Get-Rs-25-Cashback-on-Rs-25-Mobile-Recharge-(account-Specific).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="FreeCharge – Get Rs 25 Cashback on Rs 25 Mobile Recharge (account Specific)" /><published>2017-06-05T09:24:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-06-05T09:24:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/freecharge/2017/06/05/FreeCharge-%E2%80%93-Get-Rs-25-Cashback-on-Rs-25-Mobile-Recharge-(account-Specific)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/freecharge/2017/06/05/FreeCharge-Get-Rs-25-Cashback-on-Rs-25-Mobile-Recharge-(account-Specific).html">&lt;h4&gt;How to Get Rs 25 Cashback on Rs 25 Recharge at FreeCharge&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Firstly goto FreeCharge &lt;a href=&quot;https://FreeCharge.in/mobile&quot;&gt;Mobile Site&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.FreeCharge.in&quot;&gt;Desktop Site&lt;/a&gt; or Download &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.freecharge.android&quot;&gt;Android App&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Install &amp;amp; Open the FreeCharge App.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Login/Sign up your Account on FreeCharge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Now Initiate a Recharge of Rs 25 or above&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Apply Coupon:- CB25&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Once your Promo code is Applied successfully then Make the Payment using Debit/Credit card only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) You will get your Cashback in your FreeCharge wallet within 24 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Terms &amp;amp; Conditions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Valid on successful Recharges/Bill Payments done till 09th June 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Valid on Min recharge of Rs 25. Max cashback of Rs 25&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) CB25 promocode has to be applied to avail cashback offer &amp;amp; is linked yashveer@gmail .com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Valid only once per User/ Credit/ Debit Card/ Mobile Number&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Valid on Credit/Debit card.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Cashback will be credited to your Freecharge Wallet which can be redeemed within 185 days from date of credit, and is non transferable&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Not valid on Virtual Cards &amp;amp; International Cards which are issued outside India.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) Not valid for Add Cash &amp;amp; Airtel Postpaid/Prepaid/DTH/Landline&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) Offer valid only on Freecharge App, Web &amp;amp; mWeb.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">How to Get Rs 25 Cashback on Rs 25 Recharge at FreeCharge</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Airtel Broadband Plan Offer – Get 1000GB 4G Data Free For 1 Year</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/airtel/2017/06/04/Airtel-Broadband-Plan-Offer-Get-1000GB-4G-Data-Free-For-1-Year.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Airtel Broadband Plan Offer – Get 1000GB 4G Data Free For 1 Year" /><published>2017-06-04T17:57:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-06-04T17:57:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/airtel/2017/06/04/Airtel-Broadband-Plan-Offer-%E2%80%93-Get-1000GB-4G-Data-Free-For-1-Year</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/airtel/2017/06/04/Airtel-Broadband-Plan-Offer-Get-1000GB-4G-Data-Free-For-1-Year.html">&lt;h4&gt;How to Apply&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) First of All Visit Nearest Airtel Outlets, to Get Broadband Connection. 2). To buy Airtel Broadband please submit the documents listed below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Your Self attested photograph&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Your Photo proof of identity / signature&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Voter ID Card or Passport&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) After submitting these document to Airtel, They will setup Airtel Broadband Connection at your Location where you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Now choose your Desire plan which you want it &amp;amp; says him to Activate this offer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Finally your Airtel Broadband Plan would be activated shortly within few hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s22.postimg.org/64zs34u1t/IMG_20170603_000333-450x231.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Plans&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot;&gt;
&lt;table class=&quot;table table-condensed table-bordered&quot;&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;th&gt;RENTAL (RS)&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;th&gt;LOCAL + STD CALLS&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;th&gt;DATA&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;th&gt;BONUS DATA&lt;/th&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;899&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Unlimited&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;60 GB&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;750 GB&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;1099&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Unlimited&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;90 GB&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;1000 GB&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;1299&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Unlimited&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;125 GB&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;1000 GB&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;1499&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Unlimited&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;160 GB&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;1000 GB&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;tr&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;1799&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;Unlimited&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;220 GB&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;td&gt;1000 GB&lt;/td&gt;
  &lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Airtel Broadband Plan Offer: Official Announcement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a statement, Hemanth Kumar Guruswamy, CEO – Homes, Bharti Airtel (India) said, “Our new plans are aimed at putting India onto the digital superhighway and complement our superfast broadband offerings like ‘V-Fiber’. At Airtel, our mission is to enable a superior digital experience and offer great value to our customers. Our customers can now add to their online experience with exciting speeds backed by unmatched service reliability. We believe these new plans will also drive the adoption of high speed broadband in the country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Airtel Broadband: Know More About?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Airtel Broadband simple answer is “it depends”. Typically speeds start at about 512 Kbps and go up to 16 Mbps for most home users. Some installations may go as fast as 100Mbps or more depending primarily on the equipment used, distances involved, cabling quality, encoding techniques, and frequency spectrum available and even to some degree, end system configurations. Be aware that some DSL is sold as asymmetric or “rate-adaptive”. It is best to consult the providers in your area as to the access rates available in your area. Speeds can vary from provider to provider even if they are all servicing your area from the same central office&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">How to Apply</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Jio DTH Online Booking, Registration Site &amp;amp; Date,Dealership</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jio/2017/05/25/Jio-DTH-Online-Booking,-Registration-Site-&-Date,-Dealership.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jio DTH Online Booking, Registration Site &amp; Date,Dealership" /><published>2017-05-25T18:06:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-05-25T18:06:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jio/2017/05/25/Jio-DTH-Online-Booking,-Registration-Site-&amp;-Date,-Dealership</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jio/2017/05/25/Jio-DTH-Online-Booking,-Registration-Site-&amp;-Date,-Dealership.html">&lt;p&gt;Jio is again back  with some great functions and offers and I  will tell you all about it in my post Jio DTH Online Booking Registration. But this time it will be Jio DTH services. As we have to pay a lot for Tv recharge and their services. Also Set top box price is high of every company. So Jio will be having a lot cheaper price than other companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As Jio is using internet facility, so it is going to be a whole new experience for users. You can watch Tv online without any buffering. Also, they are having very different plans for each type of users. Some plans are also around Rs 60-100. You can have a plan according to your choice and start enjoying your DTH services by Jio. Also, it seems that Jio will be providing 3 months free DTH services to increase their number of customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here is How To Book Jio DTH&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Click On Link To Go To Reliance Jio Official Website (Links Will Be Updated Soon)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Click DTH Services&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Click Apply Now And Fill In Your Name Address , Plan , And All Other Details Including Contact Details .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Accept Terms And Conditions And Make The Payment Through Preferred Payment Mode .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Soon Jio DTH Personnels With Contact You For Installation Of Your Setup Box&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where &amp;amp; How To Online Register For Jio DTH&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can Online Register JIO DTH Once it available Online&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jio DTH Registration Will Start On Jio.com Jio’s Official Website&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You just Have To Fill The Details Of Yours&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jio DTH will Also Available On Jio Mini &amp;amp; Jio Xpress Mini Stores&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is Jio DTH Leaked Live On TV Video&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UD6JfhUgkh0&quot;&gt;Click to view video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Jio is again back with some great functions and offers and I will tell you all about it in my post Jio DTH Online Booking Registration. But this time it will be Jio DTH services. As we have to pay a lot for Tv recharge and their services. Also Set top box price is high of every company. So Jio will be having a lot cheaper price than other companies.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Jio DTH Offers, Price, Launch Date, Free 3 Months Service</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jio/2017/05/25/Jio-DTH-Offers,-Price,-Launch-Date,-Free-3-Months-Service.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jio DTH Offers, Price, Launch Date, Free 3 Months Service" /><published>2017-05-25T17:59:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-05-25T17:59:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jio/2017/05/25/Jio-DTH-Offers,-Price,-Launch-Date,-Free-3-Months-Service</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jio/2017/05/25/Jio-DTH-Offers,-Price,-Launch-Date,-Free-3-Months-Service.html">&lt;h4&gt;Jio DTH set top box picture leaked&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://s10.postimg.org/89bx2twa1/17841992_1335178549897414_2028790312_n.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;jio set top box&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jio is planning to launch its Jio DTH service very soon. As we can see in the picture Jio DTH Set Top Box is ready. We can expect the launch of Jio Broadband service and Jio DTH together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jio DTH Price,Plans and online booking,Channel List&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Launch Date	Expected - May-June 2017
Jio DTH Channels	300+ Channels With HD Channels Included
Jio DTH Price(Monthly)	Expected Rs.180-200
DTH Set-top Box Price	Expected Rs.3000
Jio DTH Booking	Starts From May 2017
Jio DTH Welcome Offer?	Rumored&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Jio DTH set top box picture leaked</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">PaytmMall – Get Rs 250 Cashback on Rs 800 Shopping</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/05/25/PaytmMall-Get-Rs-250-Cashback-on-Rs-800-Shopping.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="PaytmMall – Get Rs 250 Cashback on Rs 800 Shopping" /><published>2017-05-25T17:47:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-05-25T17:47:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/05/25/PaytmMall-%E2%80%93-Get-Rs-250-Cashback-on-Rs-800-Shopping</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/05/25/PaytmMall-Get-Rs-250-Cashback-on-Rs-800-Shopping.html">&lt;h4&gt;How to Get Rs 250 Cashback on Rs 800 Shopping at Paytm&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) First of all, &lt;a href=&quot;https://paytmmall.com&quot;&gt;Visit PaytmMall Website Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Choose the Product which you want to buy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Add the Product to your Shopping cart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Now goto your Shopping Cart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Apply Coupon:- WELCOME250CE&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) you will get the Screen Message “Promo Code Applied Successfully. Cashback will we Credited in your Paytm account with in 24 hours for Prepaid order and after 24 hours for Delivery for Cash on Delivery“.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Click on “Proceed to Pay“.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) Enter/ Update your Shipping Details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) Placed the Order using Online Payment or using Cash on Delivery ( if available ).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Terms &amp;amp; Conditions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) WELCOME250CE : Flat Rs 250 Cashback on any item above Rs. 800. For first time Paytm mall user. Download the app on Android or iOS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Minimum selling price of item must be Rs 800 Can be used only once per customer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Can only be used by new users of Paytm Mall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Can only be applied on a single item in cart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Promo codes are subject to maximum cash back amounts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Cash back acquired from promo codes to be credited within 24 hours of your product being shipped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Cash back received will be credited to your Paytm wallet Promo codes are not applicable for Cash on Delivery (COD) mode of payment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) If product purchased on EMI payment mode, Cash back gets credit post return policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) If product comes under no return policy, Cash back gets credited post 7 days of delivery date.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">How to Get Rs 250 Cashback on Rs 800 Shopping at Paytm</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Xiaomi Redmi 4 Price in India, Specifications, Features – Buy Online at Amazon on 23rd May</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/xiaomi/2017/05/21/Xiaomi-Redmi-4-Price-in-India,-Specifications,-Features-Buy-Online-at-Amazon-on-23rd-May.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Xiaomi Redmi 4 Price in India, Specifications, Features – Buy Online at Amazon on 23rd May" /><published>2017-05-21T18:33:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-05-21T18:33:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/xiaomi/2017/05/21/Xiaomi-Redmi-4-Price-in-India,-Specifications,-Features-%E2%80%93-Buy-Online-at-Amazon-on-23rd-May</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/xiaomi/2017/05/21/Xiaomi-Redmi-4-Price-in-India,-Specifications,-Features-Buy-Online-at-Amazon-on-23rd-May.html">&lt;h4&gt;How to Buy Xiaomi Redmi 4 Online From Flipkart, Amazon&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) First of all,  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.in/redmi-4/b?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;node=13713623031&amp;amp;_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=210c89-21&amp;amp;linkCode=ur2&amp;amp;linkId=d3fd3238ac958c460cce142864817282&amp;amp;camp=3638&amp;amp;creative=24630&quot;&gt;Visit Amazon Sale Page Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Now visit the product page and Click on Buy Now button.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Review your cart and then click on Place Order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Login or Sign up for your existing account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Now Enter your Delivery Address &amp;amp; other Details and click on Continue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Select your convenient Payment Method and proceed to the payment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Now complete your transaction and place your order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) That’s it. You will soon get Xiaomi Redmi 4 Flipkart delivered to your doorsteps within 2-3 days. Enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Xiaomi Redmi 4 Display:-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Xiaomi Redmi 4 Amazon flaunts an HD display on its IPS LCD screen. The 5.0-inch screen comes with a resolution of 720 x 1,280 pixels, which results from a density of 294 pixels per inch. The capacitive touchscreen responds well to multi touch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Xiaomi Redmi 4 Configuration:-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as the performance is concerned, the smartphone is fitted with a pair of quad-core Cortex A53 processors, which clocks speeds of 1.4GHz and 1.1GHz respectively. Xiaomi Redmi 4 Amazon. This already powerful processor is placed on a chipset of Qualcomm Snapdragon 430 MSM8937 and is assisted by a 2GB RAM to give you a fast multitasking and gaming experience. A GPU of Adreno 505 takes care of the graphical interface with ease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Xiaomi Redmi 4 Camera &amp;amp; Storage:-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Xiaomi Redmi 4 16GB houses a good 13MP primary camera. Moreover, features like phase detection autofocus, dual LED flash, ISO control, High Dynamic Range mode and a 2.2f aperture allows you to click pictures of4,128 x 3,096 pixels resolution and record videos of 1,920 x 1,080 at 30 frames per second. Xiaomi Redmi 4 Flipkart. The 5MP front camera too looks to be good option for selfies and video calling, especially with the presence of a 2.2f aperture value. The smartphone comes with an internal storage option of 16GB which can be further expanded upto 128GB with the help of a microSD card. Xiaomi Redmi 4 Buy Online, Xiaomi Redmi 4 Specifications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Xiaomi Redmi 4 Battery &amp;amp; Connectivity:-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Xiaomi Redmi 4 extracts all the fuel that it needs from a 4,100mAh li-polymer battery, which is enabled with quick charge feature. In the connectivity department, the smartphone offers dual 4G SIM slots, voice over LTE, Wi-Fi 802.11, a/ac/b/g/n, mobile hotspot, Bluetooth v4.1, A-GPS, Glonass and a microUSB 2.0 slot. Buy Redmi 4 Amazon Online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Xiaomi Redmi 4 Price In India &amp;amp; Availability:-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Xiaomi Redmi 4 price in India is Rs 6,999 for 2gb varient. 8999 for 3gb varient, 10999 for 4gb varient.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Xiaomi Redmi 4 Full Specifications:-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GENERAL&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Release date	March 2017&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Form factor	Touchscreen&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dimensions (mm)	141.30 x 69.60 x 8.90&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Weight (g)	156.00&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Battery capacity (mAh)	4100&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Removable battery	No&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Colours	Gold, Grey, Silver&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SAR value	NA&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DISPLAY&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Screen size (inches)	5.00&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Touchscreen	Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Resolution	720×1280 pixels&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pixels per inch (PPI)	296&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HARDWARE&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Processor	1.4GHz octa-core&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Processor make	Qualcomm Snapdragon 430&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RAM	2GB&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Internal storage	16GB&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expandable storage	Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expandable storage type	microSD&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Expandable storage up to (GB)	128&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CAMERA&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rear camera	13-megapixel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flash	Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Front camera	5-megapixel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SOFTWARE&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Operating System	Android 6.0&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Skin	MIUI 8&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CONNECTIVITY&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wi-Fi	Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wi-Fi standards supported	802.11 a/b/g/n&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GPS	Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bluetooth	Yes, v 4.10&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NFC	No&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Infrared	No&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;USB OTG	No&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Headphones	3.5mm&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;FM	No&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Number of SIMs	2&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SIM 1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SIM Type	Micro-SIM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GSM/CDMA	GSM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3G	Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4G/ LTE	Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supports 4G in India (Band 40)	Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SIM 2&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SIM Type	Nano-SIM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;GSM/CDMA	GSM&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3G	Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4G/ LTE	Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supports 4G in India (Band 40)	Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SENSORS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Compass/ Magnetometer	No&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proximity sensor	Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Accelerometer	Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ambient light sensor	Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gyroscope	Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Barometer	No&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Temperature sensor	No&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">How to Buy Xiaomi Redmi 4 Online From Flipkart, Amazon</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Lenskart Paytm Loot offer – Earn Rs.500 Paytm Cash on referring to your friend</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/lenskart/paytm/2017/05/21/Lenskart-Paytm-Loot-offer-Earn-Rs.500-Paytm-Cash-on-referring-to-your-friend.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Lenskart Paytm Loot offer – Earn Rs.500 Paytm Cash on referring to your friend" /><published>2017-05-21T09:48:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-05-21T09:48:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/lenskart/paytm/2017/05/21/Lenskart-Paytm-Loot-offer-%E2%80%93-Earn-Rs.500-Paytm-Cash-on-referring-to-your-friend</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/lenskart/paytm/2017/05/21/Lenskart-Paytm-Loot-offer-Earn-Rs.500-Paytm-Cash-on-referring-to-your-friend.html">&lt;h4&gt;Refer Lenskart &amp;amp; Earn Rs.500 Paytm cash&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) First of all, &lt;a href=&quot;http://lenskart.ref-r.com/c/i/12845/5305935&quot;&gt;click here to Visit the website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) After that, Click on “Login” &amp;amp; then Signup button&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Create a new account using your details like name, number &amp;amp; email id OR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Login via Facebook/ Google&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Use this refer code : JUSTKODB&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Done !! Now just click on “Refer &amp;amp; Earn” tab from home page&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) You will see your referral code there, just copy it &amp;amp; share it with the other people&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) When your friend will purchase from Lenskart, then you will receive a Rs.500 Paytm voucher (after 15 days of the delivery of the product).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Refer Lenskart &amp;amp; Earn Rs.500 Paytm cash</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Grofers – Get Flat 50% off on Lots of items</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/grofers/2017/05/21/Grofers-Get-Flat-50-off-on-Lots-of-items.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Grofers – Get Flat 50% off on Lots of items" /><published>2017-05-21T09:05:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-05-21T09:05:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/grofers/2017/05/21/Grofers-%E2%80%93-Get-Flat-50%25-off-on-Lots-of-items</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/grofers/2017/05/21/Grofers-Get-Flat-50-off-on-Lots-of-items.html">&lt;h4&gt;How to Get 50% Off on Grofers&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) First of all, &lt;a href=&quot;https://grofers.com/cln//clid/591ee3846d10fe8f0491072e&quot;&gt;Visit Grofers 50% Off Page Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Choose the Product which you want to buy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Add to Your Shopping cart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Now select your Delivery Locality&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Sign up for New account on Grofers by entering your Mobile number and verify it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Apply coupon code – No Coupon required&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Now enter your Delivery address &amp;amp; time, etc. and proceed for payment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) Place the order, You will get the 100% Cashback to your Grofers wallet within 24-48 hours.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">How to Get 50% Off on Grofers</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Droom.in – Get Helmet at Rs 9 only on 23rd May</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/droom/2017/05/21/Droom.in-Get-Helmet-at-Rs-9-only-on-23rd-May.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Droom.in – Get Helmet at Rs 9 only on 23rd May" /><published>2017-05-21T08:56:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-05-21T08:56:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/droom/2017/05/21/Droom.in-%E2%80%93-Get-Helmet-at-Rs-9-only-on-23rd-May</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/droom/2017/05/21/Droom.in-Get-Helmet-at-Rs-9-only-on-23rd-May.html">&lt;h4&gt;How to Get Helmet at Rs 9 only from Droom.in&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) First of all, &lt;a href=&quot;http://droom.in/get-set-helmet&quot;&gt;Visit the Offer Page Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Enter your Name, Mobile number, email and Submit it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note:- Site might be Very Busy, So Try on Droom App for Checkout&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) That’s it, The sale is on 23rd May at 11 am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) They will remind you via SMS and Email before sale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Hurry and register for sale before time runs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Use Coupon:- GETHELMET&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Also Sign up on droom for Fast Checkout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Droom.in Website&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in April 2014 in Silicon Valley, Droom is India’s first &amp;amp; largest marketplace to buy and sell new and used automobiles and automobile services. Droom has taken a completely innovative and disruptive approach to build trust and pricing advantages for buyers.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">How to Get Helmet at Rs 9 only from Droom.in</summary></entry></feed>