<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-05-20T20:48:29+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Offer</title><subtitle>Offers, Deals, Promo codes, Freebies. 
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Airtel Free 500 MB 4G Data For 30 Days Instantly In All Numbers</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/airtel/2017/05/20/Airtel-Free-500-MB-4G-Data-For-30-Days-Instantly-In-All-Numbers.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Airtel Free 500 MB 4G Data For 30 Days Instantly In All Numbers" /><published>2017-05-20T20:23:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-05-20T20:23:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/airtel/2017/05/20/Airtel-Free-500-MB-4G-Data-For-30-Days-Instantly-In-All-Numbers</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/airtel/2017/05/20/Airtel-Free-500-MB-4G-Data-For-30-Days-Instantly-In-All-Numbers.html">&lt;h3&gt;How To Get Airtel Free 500 MB Internet 4G Data&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1)First Of All Just Download The MyAirtel App From Playstore / Or Just Update it If You Already Have&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2)Now Just Open The MyAirtel App &amp;amp; Open The “Apps” Option from Header Of The App&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3)There You See Banner Of Airtel Movies App – With INSTALL &amp;amp; GET 500 MB Tag&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4)Just Click On Install Button&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5)After Installing Airtel Movies App Just Open It &amp;amp; Register With Your Airtel Number&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6)Post Successful Registration You Will Get Another SMS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Done !!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">How To Get Airtel Free 500 MB Internet 4G Data</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fastrack Analog Watch For Men At Rs.692 - MRP: Rs.1,395</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/flipkart/2017/05/20/Fastrack-Analog-Watch-For-Men-At-Rs.692-MRP-Rs.1,395.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fastrack Analog Watch For Men At Rs.692 - MRP: Rs.1,395" /><published>2017-05-20T17:55:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-05-20T17:55:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/flipkart/2017/05/20/Fastrack-Analog-Watch-For-Men-At-Rs.692---MRP:-Rs.1,395</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/flipkart/2017/05/20/Fastrack-Analog-Watch-For-Men-At-Rs.692-MRP-Rs.1,395.html">&lt;h3&gt;BEST LOOT DEALS OF THE DAY :&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fastrack NG3120SL01C Bare Basic Analog Watch – For Men&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://rukminim1.flixcart.com/image/832/832/watch/m/u/f/3120sl01-fastrack-original-imaeymyukdgzxqxf.jpeg?q=70&quot; alt=&quot;Fastrack NG3120SL01C Bare Basic Analog Watch&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link : &lt;a href=&quot;https://dl.flipkart.com/dl/fastrack-ng3120sl01c-bare-basic-analog-watch-men/p/itmdwgampkyhgqsg?affid=justinech1&quot;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Offer : At Rs.692(MRP: Rs.1,395)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LYF Earth 1 (White, 32 GB)  (3 GB RAM)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://rukminim1.flixcart.com/image/832/832/mobile/n/z/7/lyf-earth-1-ls-5501-original-imaemn4vqafxer4h.jpeg?q=70&quot; alt=&quot;LYF Earth 1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link : &lt;a href=&quot;https://dl.flipkart.com/dl/lyf-earth-1-white-32-gb/p/itmeg9bjzybk76mh?affid=justinech1&quot;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Offer : At Rs.9,999 (MRP: Rs.19,499)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">BEST LOOT DEALS OF THE DAY :</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How To Create A Savings Account On Paytm Payments Bank</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/05/20/How-To-Create-A-Savings-Account-On-Paytm-Payments-Bank.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How To Create A Savings Account On Paytm Payments Bank" /><published>2017-05-20T16:41:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-05-20T16:41:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/05/20/How-To-Create-A-Savings-Account-On-Paytm-Payments-Bank</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/05/20/How-To-Create-A-Savings-Account-On-Paytm-Payments-Bank.html">&lt;p&gt;India’s fastest growing digital payments provider mobile app Paytm has recently launched their payments bank. Like regular bank accounts of India, users can create current &amp;amp; saving accounts in Paytm Payments bank. Paytm will also provide credit, debit and net banking facility if you create your account on Paytm Payments bank. In this article, we will share the complete guide on how you can create a savings account or current account on Paytm Payments bank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other facilities of Paytm payment bank are you can receive money anytime anywhere. This made the process of sending and receiving money pretty faster and easier. Now, let me introduce you with Payments Bank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Definition Of A Payments Bank&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can use it as a regular bank account. But it comes with some extra useful advantages which can not be found in other banks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bank Balance Limits&lt;/strong&gt;: – The minimum balance that can be is Rs 1 only. That means you can spend all of your funds from Paytm Payments bank. Just leave Rs 1 only &amp;amp; it will keep your account running. The maximum balance is Rs 1,00,000. However, if you need to deposit more than 1 lakh, then you have to choose another bank account to continue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it will keep your Paytm Payments bank account safe. You can use it like an all time wallet. Deposit small and spend small.  There is no risk of loss. You do not need to use your bank account again and again to spend smaller amounts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Lending Allowed:&lt;/strong&gt; – Unlike other ordinary banks, Paytm Payments bank does not provide services like loans, pension funds, mutual funds, insurance. However, you can still avail them for you by contacting to them. Paytm used to tie up with other banks to provide these services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Debit Card:&lt;/strong&gt; – The big thing is you will get a debit card to spend money at online shopping stores and other places where card required. Just use your Paytm debit card to spend from your paytm wallet anytime anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:red&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;How To Create A Savings Account On Paytm Payments Bank&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Making a savings bank account on Paytm Payments bank is easy. Just keep your KYC documents ready, to begin with, Paytm Payments bank. Follow the steps given below to make savings account on Paytm Payments bank easily in no time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;No.1 Make A Paytm Account&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow below steps to create a Paytm account if you have not created one for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) At first, go to &lt;a href=&quot;https://paytm.com/&quot;&gt;paytm website here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) You can also register yourself on Paytm using their mobile app. &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=net.one97.paytm&quot;&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to download from Google Play Store.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Click on “Sign Up”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Enter your mobile phone number, valid email address and a secure password.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Check on “I hereby certify that I am 18 years of age” and hit “Create Your Paytm Wallet” button.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Now they will send a one-time password to your given mobile phone number.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Verify your number by entering the one-time password.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) That is it. You have successfully created your Paytm account. Now go to the next step to create a savings bank account on Paytm Payments bank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;No.2 Add Money To Your Wallet&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just after creating a Paytm account for you, you can simply add your address, credit/debit cards into your Paytm account profile by visiting the &lt;a href=&quot;https://paytm.com/settings&quot;&gt;settings page here.&lt;/a&gt; Follow the easy steps described below to add money to your Paytm wallet:-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Firstly, login to your Paytm account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Then click on “Add Money” button and enter your desired loading amount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Choose payment methods like Credit, Debit, Net Banking, IMPS or ATM card.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Enter card details and verify via one-time password.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) That is it. The amount will be deducted from your bank account and will be added to your Paytm wallet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can also save your card details for future transactions. Minimum add money to Paytm wallet limit is Rs 10 only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;No.3 Upgrade Your Paytm Wallet &amp;amp; Be A Paytm VIP Customer&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to upgrade your paytm wallet by filling up the KYC form. For that, you will require some of your documents which are listed on &lt;a href=&quot;http://m.p-y.tm/kyc&quot;&gt;Paytm KYC Form page.&lt;/a&gt; Just download the form and attach all the required documents like address proof, identity card &amp;amp; a passport size photograph of yours. As evidence, take a xerox copy of your Aadhar card and put your signature on that copy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, visit your nearest Paytm office with all original documents with self-attested copies. Take a copy and original of your PAN card if you want to transfer more than Rs 50,000 in one transaction. After submitting your KYC documents, upgrade process can take up to 72 hours to be completed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;No.4 Migrate From Normal Paytm Wallet To Paytm Payments Bank&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remember one thing; you cannot migrate your paytm wallet to paytm payments bank until you complete your KYC verification and upgrade your wallet. After completing the previous steps, it shall automatically migrate your standard paytm wallet to paytm payments bank.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, if you do not want to migrate your paytm wallet, you need to send a request to them. However, if you do so, your Paytm wallet will be closed permanently. Because from 2017, Paytm started migrating all the paytm wallets to paytm payments bank automatically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How to Get Passbook, Debit Card &amp;amp; Chequebook of Your Paytm Savings Bank Account&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After completing the above processes, a banking kit will be shipped to your address. This kit will contain your passbook, chequebook, your paytm debit card, internet banking user manual and a welcome kit. It can take up to 14 days to be shipped to your address.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope this A-Z Paytm Payments bank guide will help you to open or make an account on Paytm Payments Bank. Now, it is your turn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you want to get started with Paytm Payments Bank?
Do you have any queries about Paytm bank?
Have you already created an account for you?
How good or bad is your experience with Paytm Payments bank?
Please leave your answers in the comment section below. We will try to answer all of your questions regarding the process of creating an account on Paytm Payments bank. Don’t forget to subscribe to our blog to get latest updates instantly.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">India’s fastest growing digital payments provider mobile app Paytm has recently launched their payments bank. Like regular bank accounts of India, users can create current &amp;amp; saving accounts in Paytm Payments bank. Paytm will also provide credit, debit and net banking facility if you create your account on Paytm Payments bank. In this article, we will share the complete guide on how you can create a savings account or current account on Paytm Payments bank.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Paytm Mall – Get Flat 50% Cashback on LeD Bulbs</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/05/20/Paytm-Mall-Get-Flat-50-Cashback-on-LeD-Bulbs.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Paytm Mall – Get Flat 50% Cashback on LeD Bulbs" /><published>2017-05-20T14:25:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-05-20T14:25:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/05/20/Paytm-Mall-%E2%80%93-Get-Flat-50%25-Cashback-on-LeD-Bulbs</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/05/20/Paytm-Mall-Get-Flat-50-Cashback-on-LeD-Bulbs.html">&lt;h3&gt;How to Get Flat 50% Cashback on LeD Bulbs&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) First of all, &lt;a href=&quot;https://paytmmall.com/shop/g/home-kitchen-store/led-flash&quot;&gt;Visit 50% Cashback on LeD Bulbs Page Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Choose the Product which you want to buy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Add the Product to your Shopping cart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Now goto your Shopping Cart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Apply Coupon:- HOME50&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) You will get the Screen Message “Promo Code Applied Successfully“.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Click on “Proceed to Pay“.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) Enter/ Update your Shipping Details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) Placed the Order using Online Payment or using Cash on Delivery ( if available ).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:red&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Features&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Does not emit dangerous UV-rays&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) 40% Energy saving over CFL&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) 80% Energy saving over GLS bulb&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Eco friendly&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) 806 lumen light output&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) 6500 K color temperature&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) 150 degree beam angle&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">How to Get Flat 50% Cashback on LeD Bulbs</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">PhonePe App – Get 20% Cashback on Prepaid Mobile Recharge (5 Times)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/phonepe/2017/05/20/PhonePe-App-Get-20-Cashback-on-Prepaid-Mobile-Recharge-(5-Times).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="PhonePe App – Get 20% Cashback on Prepaid Mobile Recharge (5 Times)" /><published>2017-05-20T14:14:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-05-20T14:14:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/phonepe/2017/05/20/PhonePe-App-%E2%80%93-Get-20%25-Cashback-on-Prepaid-Mobile-Recharge-(5-Times)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/phonepe/2017/05/20/PhonePe-App-Get-20-Cashback-on-Prepaid-Mobile-Recharge-(5-Times).html">&lt;h3&gt;How to Get 20% Cashback on Prepaid Mobile Recharge at PhonePe App&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) First of all, &lt;a href=&quot;https://phone.pe/ru_just1ju43&quot;&gt;Download PhonePe app Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Install &amp;amp; Open the Phone App.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Slide screen and Sign up for account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Verify your Mobile number via OTP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) And complete minor process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Now Select your Bank then they fetch your details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Now Initiate a Prepaid Mobile Recharge&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) Enter your Mobile number, operator, amount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) Pay the amount UPI, Phonepe wallet or CC/DC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10) You will get the Rs 20 Cashback instantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:red&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Terms &amp;amp; Conditions&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) This offer gives 20% cashback (up to Rs 20) per transaction for Prepaid Mobile Recharges.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Cashback is eligible only for Mobile Recharges through UPI, Phonepe wallet &amp;amp; CC/DC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Cashback will be credited to the PhonePe wallet within one working day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Offer valid from 2nd May 2017 12:00 noon to 31st May 2017 23:59 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Offer valid up to 5 transactions per Phonepe registered user/smartphone during the offer period and applicable for both android and IOS devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) The transaction must be initiated and completed by the user within the PhonePe app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) PhonePe has the right to amend the terms &amp;amp; conditions, end the offer, or call back any or all its offers without prior notice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) In a case of dispute, PhonePe reserves the right to a final decision on the interpretation of these Terms &amp;amp; Conditions.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">How to Get 20% Cashback on Prepaid Mobile Recharge at PhonePe App</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Paytm Loot – Get Rs 55 Free Paytm Cash using Digital Gold Trick</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/05/20/Paytm-Loot-Get-Rs-55-Free-Paytm-Cash-using-Digital-Gold-Trick.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Paytm Loot – Get Rs 55 Free Paytm Cash using Digital Gold Trick" /><published>2017-05-20T13:37:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-05-20T13:37:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/05/20/Paytm-Loot-%E2%80%93-Get-Rs-55-Free-Paytm-Cash-using-Digital-Gold-Trick</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/05/20/Paytm-Loot-Get-Rs-55-Free-Paytm-Cash-using-Digital-Gold-Trick.html">&lt;h3&gt;How to Get Rs 55 Paytm Cash on Purchase of Digital Gold:-&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) First of all, &lt;a href=&quot;https://paytm.com/digitalgold&quot;&gt;Visit Paytm Buy Page Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Select “Buy in Rupee” Now buy Gold worth Rs 1000.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Apply Coupon code:- GOLDNEW10&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Once coupon code get applied Successfully, then Pay Rs 1000 via Paytm Wallet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Now You will get the Rs 100 cashback in your Paytm wallet instantly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) &lt;a href=&quot;https://paytm.com/digitalgold&quot;&gt;Visit Digital Gold Page again&lt;/a&gt; and Click on “Sell“.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Enter amount as Rs 954 to 955.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) Enter your Bank Account no. &amp;amp; IFSC Code on Next Page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) Pay Rs 10 as Convenience charge. Use Coupon:- MAYGOLD1 to Get Rs 10 cashback on Convenience charge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10) Sell &amp;amp; Get Rs 955 directly in your Bank Account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;11) Now Calculate- You have Paid Rs 1000 and Got Rs 955 in Bank account + 100 Cashback in Paytm wallet using Coupon code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total – Paid-1000 &amp;amp; Got-1055&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Benefit – Flat Rs 55 per Paytm Account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;12) Enjoy !!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How to Sell Gold [Latest Update]:-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) &lt;a href=&quot;https://paytm.com/digitalgold&quot;&gt;Visit DigitalGold Page Here&lt;/a&gt; and Click on “Sell”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Enter amount Rs 942 (Price might change from time to time).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note:- If your Yesterday transaction is in Pending process, then Cancle it to Get Refund of Rs 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Enter Bank details and Apply Coupon:- MAYGOLD1 to get Rs 10 Cashback within 24 hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Sell and Get Rs 942 directly in your Bank account.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">How to Get Rs 55 Paytm Cash on Purchase of Digital Gold:-</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Paytm Promo Code May 2017 - Recharge &amp;amp; Bill Payments Offers</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/05/20/Paytm-Promo-Code-May-2017-Recharge-and-Bill-Payments-Offers.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Paytm Promo Code May 2017 - Recharge &amp; Bill Payments Offers" /><published>2017-05-20T13:10:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-05-20T13:10:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/05/20/Paytm-Promo-Code-May-2017---Recharge-and-Bill-Payments-Offers</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/paytm/2017/05/20/Paytm-Promo-Code-May-2017-Recharge-and-Bill-Payments-Offers.html">&lt;h3&gt;Get 50% Cashback on Booking Movie Tickets (Max 150)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paytm has come up with Booking Movie Tickets Offer where you will get the 50% Cashback upto a Maximum of Rs 150 on purchase of 2 Movie Tickets and No Minimum Purchase required. Apply Coupon:- GBON50 or MOVIE50&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Get 100% Cashback on your First Bus Booking (Max cb Rs 200)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paytm has come up with awesome deal on Bus Ticket Booking where they are offering Flat 100% Cashback on Bus Ticket Booking for First time Bus Ticket booking usinf code FREEBUS. No minimum Bus Ticket booking. Maximum cashback is Rs 200. So Hurry up !!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Paytm Jio Coupons&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recharge your Jio number with Rs.303/Rs.499 pack at Paytm using code PAYTMJIO and get Rs.30 discount. You can avail this offer 2 times in March 2017. That’s not all; After successful recharge, you will also get Rs.150 cashback on booking 2 movie tickets using MOVIE4JIO code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Enjoy 4% Cashback Upto Rs.200&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now you can avail 4% cashback upto Rs.200 in your paytm wallet by applying paytm coupon code “GRAB4”. The best thing is this offer is valid for both old and new users and valid on Prepaid, Postpaid, DTH, Datacard Recharge, Landline payments. You can avail this offer five times only.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Stand a Chance to Win Recharge For a Year&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an excellent offer by paytm where you can get an opportunity to win free mobile recharge for a year. To be eligible for this offer, you just need to make at least one bill payment by using paytm coupons “BILLFREE”. The minimum bill payment amount must be Rs.100. The winners are selected through a Lucky Draw. Top 51 spenders will be awarded recharge for a year. If you win, then you will get Rs. 200 every month till 12 months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Avail Rs.10 Cashback Every Month&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is another great offer for all users where you can get Rs.10 cashback with no minimum transaction. However, there is a twist, to active this offer, firstly you have to make your recharge with Rs.100 or more by applying paytm promo code “LOOT” or “GRAB100“. You will get Rs.10 cashback on that recharge. After successful transaction, you can use the same promo code for next ten months to get Rs 10 cashback every month&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;4% Cashback on DTH Recharge&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy 4% Cashback upto Rs.200 on DTH Recharge, Apply paytm coupon TSKY4 in the promo code box. Valid for Tata Sky users. The same offer can be availed by Videocon DTH, Sun Direct DTH, Big TV Dish TV users by Applying paytm coupon codes VD2H4, SD4, RBTV4 &amp;amp; DTV4 respectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;100% Cashback for Lucky 7 Users&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just use coupon code “LUCKY7” on your prepaid/ DTH/ Data card recharge, Landline or Postpaid bill payments and win 100% cashback. The maximum cashback amount is Rs.100. Seven lucky winners will get 100% cashback every hour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Upto Rs.10 Cashback on Recharge &amp;amp; Bill Payments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apply Paytm Promo Code “GRAB10” when you make any transaction at Paytm and get Rs.1 cashback. The minimum transaction amount is Rs.50. This offer can be availed ten times per user. Means you can earn upto Rs.10 cashback.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Win 1 Lakh Cashback Daily&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paytm has come up with a fantastic offer where you can win 1 Lakh cashback daily. The best thing is Airtel users can also participate in this offer. Use more paytm services like booking movie, bus, flight tickets, etc. and make maximum transactions to make chances higher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Rs 50 Cashback on Prepaid Electricity Bill Payments&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are going to make your Prepaid Electricity bill payments using the Paytm app, then do not forget to apply paytm promo code “POWER”. Because after using the code you will get Rs.50 cashback. This offer is valid for all users and is applicable only on minimum transaction of Rs.500&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Get 10% Cashback on Delhi &amp;amp; Mumbai Metro Card Recharger&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now Recharge your Metro Cards and travel cheaply in your city. Paytm is now offering 10% Cashback on Metro Card Recharge. Maximum Cashback is Rs. 100. Promocode can be used 1 times per user. Apply coupon:- METRO10&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Metro Card Recharge Offer&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use paytm promo code “RIDE” on your metro card recharge and get Rs.20 cashback. Valid only on the first &amp;amp; second transaction of Delhi Metro or Mumbai Metro. You will get Rs.10 cashback on 1st &amp;amp; 2nd Metro recharge of Rs 100 or more. Valid for 2times per user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Paytm Add Money and Signup Offers&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this section, we will provide you with all working paytm add money offers for all users. So guys start adding money in your paytm wallet and avail additional cashback. Also use your wallet balance for the cashless transaction and earn extra cashback.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Avail Free Rs 20 or 15 Wallet Balance&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paytm has come up with a fantastic add money offer, especially for new users where you can get Rs.20 free paytm cash by applying paytm coupons FREE20 or FIRST20. Use FREE15 code to get Rs.15 in your wallet. So guys hurry up because this offer is valid for limited time only. Also try FREE25, FREE10 or GET10 codes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Upto Rs 75 Recharge For New Users&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, you heard it right. Now create your new account on paytm and get Rs.25 cashback on Rs.100 recharge. You just need to apply paytm coupons “PAYTMAPP” to avail this signup offer. Use the same code for three times and enjoy upto Rs.75 cashback on your recharge and bill payments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Pay Using Paytm Wallet and Save Big&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Presenting you “pay with paytm wallet” offers where you can get extra cash back by making payments through your paytm wallet. Just use your paytm wallet to make payments at the time of shopping on your favourite sites like Dominos, Zomato, Swiggy, Foodpanda, etc. and earn cashback on purchasing Gift Cards&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Buy Gift cards and Avail Cashback&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will get 10% cashback on purchasing gift cards of Lifestyle, Dominos and Pizza Hut. Also buy gift cards of Bigbazaar, CCD, Baskin Robbins, Westside and more to get 5% cashback. &lt;a href=&quot;https://paytm.com/shop/h/gift-cards&quot;&gt;Visit here&lt;/a&gt; to avail paytm gift card offers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Order on Foodpanda &amp;amp; Get 20% Cashback&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now order food online at Foodpanda and get 20% cashback. To avail the offer, make the payment via Paytm wallet only. Maximum cashback of Rs.100 can be availed for this offer and valid two transactions per user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Paytm Uber Offer: 2 Rides Free&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now Link your Paytm wallet on Uber app and then Use paytm coupons “DEAL150” during checkout to get two free rides.You need to transact using Paytm Wallet to avail the offer. Maximum discount of Rs 75 on each ride. This offer is valid for new Uber user only&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Paytm Bus, Flight, Movie Offers&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Book tickets for flights, bus, hotel, movie, etc. at Paytm app and earn extra cashback. Now paytm has added some new features like movie ticket booking, hotel booking, etc. So guys try new features of Paytm and enjoy cashback using below mentioned paytm coupons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Rs 100 Cashback on Bus Booking&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enjoy Rs.100 cashback on booking bus tickets. Your minimum transaction value should be Rs.750. Apply “FEBBUS“ in the promo code section while booking bus tickets at paytm. This Offer Valid from 1st Feb 17 to 28th Feb 17.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Flat Rs 500 Cashback on Flight Bookings&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have to use paytm promo code “FLY500” to grab Rs.500 cashback at the time of booking flights at Paytm app. Minimum order value of Rs.5000 and is valid six times per user. &lt;a href=&quot;https://paytm.com/flights&quot;&gt;Visit Here to Book Now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;100% Cashback on Booking Movie Tickets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will get 100% cashback upto Rs.100. Just open your paytm and book your favourite movie by using “WOW” paytm promo code and get 100% cashback.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;100% Cashback on Booking Movie Tickets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will get 100% cashback upto Rs.100. Just open your paytm and book your favourite movie by using “WOW” paytm promo code and get 100% cashback.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:red&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;How to Use Paytm Coupons at Paytm App&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1)Firstly, Download the App from Google pay store&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2)Now Install and Open the app&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3)Signup your account by providing your name, email ID &amp;amp; Mobile number&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4)Verify your mobile number using OTP &amp;amp; email ID by clicking verification link&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5)Now on dashboard, you will see “Recharge &amp;amp; Bill Payments” option&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6)Initiate a prepaid/ postpaid/ DTH recharge&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7)Apply Paytm coupons &amp;amp; Proceed to checkout&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8)Make your payment using net banking, debit or credit cards&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9)Bingo!! You will receive your cashback as well as recharge instantly.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Get 50% Cashback on Booking Movie Tickets (Max 150)</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Flipkart Big 10 Sale, Its Much Bigger Get upto 80% OFF+10% via HDFC Credit Card</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/flipkart/2017/05/14/Flipkart-Big-10-Sale,-Get-upto-80-OFF-+-10-via-HDFC-Credit-Card.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Flipkart Big 10 Sale, Its Much Bigger Get upto 80% OFF+10% via HDFC Credit Card" /><published>2017-05-14T13:21:46+05:30</published><updated>2017-05-14T13:21:46+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/flipkart/2017/05/14/Flipkart-Big-10-Sale,-Get-upto-80%25-OFF-+-10%25-via-HDFC-Credit-Card</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/flipkart/2017/05/14/Flipkart-Big-10-Sale,-Get-upto-80-OFF-+-10-via-HDFC-Credit-Card.html">&lt;h3&gt;How to avail Flipkart Big 10 Sale Offers &amp;amp; Deals:-&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) First of all, &lt;a href=&quot;http://dl.flipkart.com/dl/?affid=justinech1&quot;&gt;Visit Flipkart Website Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Search or choose the product which you want to buy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Click on “Buy Now’.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Add the Product to your Shopping Cart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Login/Sign up on Flipkart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Enter your Shipping Address/details.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Finally Select any Payment mode and Pay the amount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) Place the Order and Your Order will be delivered in 2-4 working days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) Choose Payment mode as HDFC Credit card for 10% Discount or Choose Payment mode as PhonePe App for 30% Discount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color:red&quot;&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Important note:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you choose HDFC card offer details are,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Offer duration -14th May, 2017 (00:00 hours) to 18th May, 2017 (23:59 hours)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum net cart value, i.e. total cart value of ‘Eligible products’, should be more than INR 6,499&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maximum discount per card is INR 1,500&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you choose phonepe app, details are&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Offer is valid from May 14, 2017 (00:00 hrs) to May 18, 2017 (11:59 hrs) (“ Offer Period”).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maximum cashback that can be availed during the offer period is Rs. 300&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cashback will apply only on the first transaction during the offer period.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This offer can’t be clubbed with hdfc bank offer.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">How to avail Flipkart Big 10 Sale Offers &amp;amp; Deals:-</summary></entry></feed>